Paul Baran Papers M1817
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- C & C Fdn. Date:020401 (Container 148, Folder 11)
  Request for 2002 C & C Prize Nomination (s)
- PB Publications Date:600823 (Container 149, Folder 1)
  1960 IRE WESCON Convention Record (PB - "An Adaptive Character Reader")
- PB Publications Date:650001 (Container 149, Folder 2)
  AFIPS Conference Proceedings - Computers: Their Impact on Society" (PB - Communications, Computers & People")
- PB Publications Date:670601 (Container 149, Folder 3)
  The Public Internet (PB - "The Future Computer Utility")
- PB Publications Date:671001 (Container 149, Folder 4)
  Changing Marketing Systems AMA Winter Conference Proceedings
- PB Publications Date:670320 (Container 149, Folder 5)
  1967 IEEE International Convention DIGEST
- PB Publications Date:680318 (Container 149, Folder 6)
  1968 IEEE International Convention DIGEST
- PB Publications Date:680625 (Container 149, Folder 7)
  1968 Computer Group Conference
- PB Publications Date:690401 (Container 149, Folder 8)
  Law & Contemporary Problems: Communications Part I
- PB Publications Date:690401 (Container 149, Folder 9)
- PB Publications Date:770001 (Container 149, Folder 10)
  Information Processing 77
- PB Publications Date:770701 (Container 149, Folder 11)
  Technology and Privacy - Report of Privacy Protection Study Commission
- PB Publications Date:781101 (Container 149, Folder 12)
  Proceedings of the IEEE Special Issue on Packet Communications
- PB Publications Date:891001 (Container 149, Folder 13)
  Computer Communication Review SIGCOMM (PB - winner of 1989 SIGCOM Award)
- PB Publications Date:900001 (Container 149, Folder 14)
  Packet Switching by PB
- PB Publications Date:900001 (Container 149, Folder 15)
- PB Publications Date:900001 (Container 149, Folder 16)
- PB Publications Date:901006 (Container 149, Folder 17)
  IEEE 1990 Medals Presentation - PB won Alexander Graham Bell Medal
- PB Publications Date:590501 (Container 150, Folder 1)
  A Probability Matrix Pattern Comparator (Baran Thesis)
- PB Publications Date:670320 (Container 150, Folder 2)
  1967 IEEE International Convention Record
- PB Publications Date:700201 (Container 150, Folder 3)
  Notes on a Seminar on Future Broad-Band Communications (by Baran)
- PB Publications Date:700001 (Container 150, Folder 4)
  The Computer Impact (Baran p. 81)
- PB Publications Date:710901 (Container 150, Folder 5)
  The Future of the Telephone Industry (by Baran and Lipinski)
- PB Publications Date:710901 (Container 150, Folder 6)
- PB Publications Date:711014 (Container 150, Folder 7)
  Digital Systems Viewed as Communications Media (AFIPS Workshop)
- PB Publications Date:710627 (Container 150, Folder 8)
  42nd Annual Meeting - The Telephone Association of Canada
- PB Publications Date:720127 (Container 150, Folder 9)
  Information Technology: some Critical Implications for Decision Making
- PB Publications Date:720101 (Container 150, Folder 10)
  Bell Telephone Magazine
- PB Publications Date:750101 (Container 150, Folder 11)
  IEEE Transactions on Communications (Baran p. 5)
- PB Publications Date:750101 (Container 150, Folder 12)
- PB Publications Date:760401 (Container 150, Folder 13)
  Networks: An International Journal
- PB Publications Date:760601 (Container 150, Folder 14)
  Computer Networks: the International Journal of Distributed Informatique
- PB Publications Date:790115 (Container 150, Folder 15)
  Proceedings of the IEEE (Special Issue on Packet Communications Networks)
- PB Publications Date:890001 (Container 150, Folder 16)
  Growing Vulnerability of the Public Switched Networks
- PB Publications Date:890001 (Container 150, Folder 17)
- PB Publications Date:890919 (Container 150, Folder 19)
  Communications Architectures & Protocols
- Miscellaneous (Container 151)
  Stuff that should be filed elsewhere
- Correspondence Date:850101 (Container 153, Folder 1)
  Metricom, Interfax, Packet (1985-87)
- Correspondence Date:880101 (Container 153, Folder 2)
  Personal correspondence
- Correspondence Date:930101 (Container 153, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Date:950101 (Container 153, Folder 4)
  Kinney & Lange
- Correspondence Date:960318 (Container 153, Folder 5)
  Nat'l Acad Sci Review of Report (Semenza)
- Addresses & Tel. Date:841231 (Container 154, Folder 1)
  List of CableDate Shareholders. Tel. & Addresses; Packet Cable correspondence
- Addresses & Tel. Date:850924 (Container 154, Folder 2)
  PacketCable Address List
- Addresses & Tel. Date:900131 (Container 154, Folder 3)
  Telebit Address List
- Addresses & Tel. Date:920802 (Container 154, Folder 4)
  InterFax Address List
- Addresses & Tel. Date:940913 (Container 154, Folder 5)
  Addresses - Friends and Colleagues
- PB Files 4000-4062 (Container 158)
  Awards: Drexel, UCLA
- Topics 1020-1406 box 3 (Container 159)
- TSTV (Container 160)
  Primary Component Tech Data
- Miscellaneous Date:880101 (Container 161, Folder 1)
  Cable TV: IEEE " Fiber to the Home - Practically a Reality" and 12 other articles
- Miscellaneous Date:880627 (Container 161, Folder 2)
  Cable TV: PB, "Relationship Between Cable-TV and the Public Switched Telephone Network in 2000"
- Miscellaneous Date:880701 (Container 161, Folder 3)
  Cable TV: "E-com Tier Guard System Applications"
- Miscellaneous Date:880815 (Container 161, Folder 4)
  Cable TV: SF Chronicle, "Phone Companies - Competition for Cable" and other articles
- Miscellaneous Date:880912 (Container 161, Folder 5)
  Cable TV: Electronic News, "House Unit Calls for National ATV Plan" and other articles
- Miscellaneous Date:881031 (Container 161, Folder 6)
  Cable TV: Multichannel News, "Viewer Fragmentation" facts on household TV's
- Miscellaneous Date:881101 (Container 161, Folder 7)
  Cable TV: IEEE/OSA Publication, "Journal of Lightwave Technology"
- Miscellaneous Date:881101 (Container 161, Folder 8)
  Cable TV: CED magazine of Broadband Technology (both Nov)
- Miscellaneous Date:881201 (Container 161, Folder 9)
  Cable TV: Cable Television Business, "The Drama of Cable's Customer Service"
- Miscellaneous Date:900514 (Container 161, Folder 10)
  Cable TV: Multichannel News, "Warner Interdiction Test Proves to be Successful" and other articles
- Miscellaneous Date:871029 (Container 161, Folder 11)
  Equatorial: "Notice of Special Meeting of Shareholders, Nov. 24, 1987"
- Miscellaneous Date:880105 (Container 161, Folder 12)
  Equatorial: "Equatorial Communications Company Acquired by Contel ASC"
- Miscellaneous Date:880105 (Container 161, Folder 13)
  New Ventures: "Fundamentals of Digital switching" (manuscript went to Plenum)
- Miscellaneous Date:890305 (Container 161, Folder 14)
  New Ventures: PB, "A Method and Device for Reducing Humidity in an Imperfectly Sealed Chamber"
- Miscellaneous Date:890317 (Container 161, Folder 15)
  New Ventures: Metrotech 610/650 (600 Series passive/Active Locator)
- Miscellaneous Date:900105 (Container 161, Folder 16)
  NRC: Science, "U. S. Trade Policy at a Crossroad"
- Miscellaneous Date:900116 (Container 161, Folder 17)
  NRC: NTIA, "Comprehensive Study of the Domestic Telecommunications infrastructure"
- Miscellaneous Date:900127 (Container 161, Folder 18)
  NRC: PB draft, "Towards a National Policy for the Information Infrastructure"
- Miscellaneous Date:891201 (Container 161, Folder 19)
  NRC: "Information Infrastructure: the Nation's Seed Corn"
- Miscellaneous Date:880101 (Container 161, Folder 20)
  Packet Technologies: "1988 Partnership Report, Interactive Cable Investors, Interactive Cable Technology"
- Miscellaneous Date:880107 (Container 161, Folder 21)
  Packet Technologies: Packet letter, fax to PB from Robertson
- Miscellaneous Date:890203 (Container 161, Folder 22)
  Packet Technologies: Minutes of the regular meeting of the Board of Directors, Dec. 19, 1988
- Miscellaneous Date:890301 (Container 161, Folder 23)
  Packet Technologies: fax from Jenett of Fenwick, Davis & West re: Packetcable/Stratacom
- Miscellaneous Date:890413 (Container 161, Folder 24)
  Packet Technologies: Packet Technologies - Stratacom stock Distribution
- Miscellaneous Date:890413 (Container 161, Folder 25)
  Packet Technologies: Documents related to StrataCom stock distribution
- Miscellaneous Date:890417 (Container 161, Folder 26)
  Packet Technologies: Transfer of Packet Technologies Stock
- Miscellaneous Date:890501 (Container 161, Folder 27)
  Packet Technologies: Forbes, "Amoco Corporation: First-Rate Company"
- Miscellaneous Date:880102 (Container 161, Folder 28)
  Pelkey Paper: "The Data Communications Industry 1968 - 1988
- Miscellaneous Date:880718 (Container 161, Folder 29)
  Pelkey Paper: Chapter 5, "Local Area and Wide Area Networks: Beginning to Scenarios"
- Miscellaneous Date:871130 (Container 161, Folder 30)
  Stratacom: Communications Week, "Codex Offers T1 users something Totally New and Unexpected"
- Miscellaneous Date:871202 (Container 161, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Date:880101 (Container 161, Folder 32)
  Stratacom: Telephone numbers for David Wood & Scott Kriens
- Miscellaneous Date:881020 (Container 161, Folder 33)
  Stratacom: Distribution of StrataCom stock - Board of Directors Meeting, Dec. 19, 1988 & other info.
- Miscellaneous Date:881101 (Container 161, Folder 34)
  Stratacom: Data Communications, "User Survey Exclusive"
- Miscellaneous Date:881212 (Container 161, Folder 35)
  Stratacom: "Bellcore Develops new packet Switch" and other articles
- Miscellaneous Date:881213 (Container 161, Folder 36)
  Stratacom: "A Codex Combination: Stat Mux packet Switches"
- Houser/Schriever Date:870101 (Container 162, Folder 1)
  (Houser) PB's "Long Term Implications: Relationship Between National Productivy & National Defense"
- Houser/Schriever Date:871201 (Container 162, Folder 2)
  (Houser) DOD/VC Initiative
- Houser/Schriever Date:880108 (Container 162, Folder 3)
  (Houser) PB Memo on VC and Defense R&D (paper for Tech. Working Group, Concept, Schriever memo)
- Houser/Schriever Date:880212 (Container 162, Folder 4)
  (Houser) Houser letter to PB regarding venture capital in gov. - meeting Feb. 22 in Wash.
- Houser/Schriever Date:880226 (Container 162, Folder 5)
  (Houser) Houser draft - new ventures
- Houser/Schriever Date:880304 (Container 162, Folder 6)
  (Houser) PB Memo on meeting with Pelkey & Nunziatto March 3, 1988
- Houser/Schriever Date:880420 (Container 162, Folder 7)
  (Houser) PB Memo to Houser re: west coast meetings report
- Houser/Schriever Date:881031 (Container 162, Folder 8)
  (Houser) Recent meetings with Under Sec. of Defense, Acquisition & his principal deputy
- Houser/Schriever Date:881214 (Container 162, Folder 9)
  (Houser) Working Group on Defense Technology Dev.; statement of purpose, etc.
- Houser/Schriever Date:890106 (Container 162, Folder 10)
  (Houser) Dunn's (DARPA Gen. Counsel) "Discussion Draft" of legislation for new charter of DARPA
- Houser/Schriever Date:890522 (Container 162, Folder 11)
  (Houser) New developments in Houser Working Group
- Houser/Schriever Date:890126 (Container 162, Folder 12)
  (Houser) Report on meeting with Congressman McCurdy
- Houser/Schriever Date:890727 (Container 162, Folder 13)
  (Houser) Progress report on Group's Activities and Results
- Houser/Schriever Date:900419 (Container 162, Folder 14)
  (Houser) Distribution List - Houser Committee
- Houser/Schriever Date:880128 (Container 162, Folder 15)
  (Schriever) PB summary draft to Rona
- Houser/Schriever Date:880208 (Container 162, Folder 16)
  (Schriever) Nunziato's letter to Gen. Schriever
- Houser/Schriever Date:880211 (Container 162, Folder 17)
  (Schriever) Fact Sheet on President's space policy & Commercial Space Initiative
- Houser/Schriever Date:880212 (Container 162, Folder 18)
  (Schriever) Houser's letter to PB confirming meeting for VC participating in Gov. R & D
- Houser/Schriever Date:880226 (Container 162, Folder 19)
  (Schriever) Houser's letter to PB regarding "Draft Report - New Ventures"
- Houser/Schriever Date:880303 (Container 162, Folder 20)
  (Schriever) PB memo regarding meeting with Pelkey & Nunziatto, March 3, 1988
- Houser/Schriever Date:880307 (Container 162, Folder 21)
  (Schriever) Nunziato's memo on formation of the new venture capital fund
- Houser/Schriever Date:871202 (Container 162, Folder 22)
  (Schriever) Nunziato's letter to Gen. Schriever re PB's paper
- Houser/Schriever Date:880108 (Container 162, Folder 23)
  (Schriever) PB's letter (to list) on Venture Capital and Defense R&D, plus 3 papers
- Houser/Schriever Date:880108 (Container 162, Folder 24)
  (Schriever) PB hand-written notes (VC partnership, not corp.)
- NRC Study Date:850701 (Container 163, Folder 1)
  Electromagnetic Pulse (EMP) - Final Report, EMP Task Force of NSTAC
- NRC Study Date:860718 (Container 163, Folder 2)
  Request for rapid assessment of program's suitability and effectiveness (860718 - 861113)
- NRC Study Date:860811 (Container 163, Folder 3)
  Wohlstetter - 2 papers on AT&T wide bandwidth switches
- NRC Study Date:860901 (Container 163, Folder 4)
  Tech. Information Bulletin: Nuclear Weapons Effects Studies for the 5ESStm Switch
- NRC Study Date:861216 (Container 163, Folder 5)
  To Adm. Boyes, "Packet Switching is good and should be pursued" etc.
- NRC Study Date:861223 (Container 163, Folder 6)
  NETS Specifications/Requirements Information
- NRC Study Date:870116 (Container 163, Folder 7)
  PB's "Some Half Thoughts on NETS", written Jan. 12, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870324 (Container 163, Folder 8)
  NETS Requirements/Implications sent to several people
- NRC Study Date:871208 (Container 163, Folder 9)
  National Security Telecommunications Committee Meeting, Dec. 8, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870504 (Container 163, Folder 10)
  Briefing to COP & COR, April 30, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870528 (Container 163, Folder 11)
  PB's "NETS in the 1985 NAS Report: Does it satisfy the 1985 Academy Report Objectives?"
- NRC Study Date:870901 (Container 163, Folder 12)
  National Security Telecommunications Committee Meeting, Sept. 1-2, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870916 (Container 163, Folder 13)
  Open Network Architectures & Broadband ISDN: the Joker in the Regulatory Deck 163 14 871030 NRC Study Call to Meeting, Dec. 8 and 9, 1987 163 15 871101 NRC Study The Next Generation Network"
- NRC Study Date:880119 (Container 163, Folder 16)
  National Security Telecommunications Committee Meeting, Jan. 19-20, 1988
- NRC Study Date:880215 (Container 163, Folder 17)
  PB's handwritten notes from Jan 19-20, 1988 meeting
- NRC Study Date:880315 (Container 163, Folder 18)
  National Security Telecommunications Committee Meeting, Mar. 15-16, 1988
- NRC Study Date:880316 (Container 163, Folder 19)
  Briefing for the National Academy of Sciences, STU-III Synchronization
- NRC Study Date:880316 (Container 163, Folder 20)
  Atlantic Research Corp. "Perspectives on Testing & Restoration & Network Management"
- NRC Study Date:880426 (Container 163, Folder 21)
  Call to Meeting, May 18-19, 1988, packet of advanced information
- NRC Study Date:880518 (Container 163, Folder 22)
  Driving Forces Which Will Shape the Public Switched Network Through the Year 2000
- NRC Study Date:880518 (Container 163, Folder 23)
  Technical Progress reports from Russia, other information
- NRC Study Date:891201 (Container 163, Folder 24)
  CNS and CSI Application, and Commercial SATCOM Interoperability (CSI)
- NRC Study Date:840101 (Container 164, Folder 1)
  National Academy of Science, National Research Council...A Temple of Science
- NRC Study Date:851201 (Container 164, Folder 2)
  DCA-EMS, "Accounts Directory & Networks Telephone Directory"
- NRC Study Date:860613 (Container 164, Folder 3)
  DCA-EMS, "User Manual"
- NRC Study Date:860701 (Container 164, Folder 4)
  The Policy Planning Environment for National Security Telecommunications
- NRC Study Date:861101 (Container 164, Folder 5)
  Bellcore View of NETS (Gifford)
- NRC Study Date:861103 (Container 164, Folder 6)
  PB hand-written notes from meeting Nov. 3-4, 1986
- NRC Study Date:861218 (Container 164, Folder 7)
  Nationwide Emergency Telecommunications Systems
- NRC Study Date:870212 (Container 164, Folder 8)
  Summary of Committee's Fourth Meeting - Feb. 12-13, 1987 (revised)
- NRC Study Date:870227 (Container 164, Folder 9)
  Call to Meeting: March 4-5, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870323 (Container 164, Folder 10)
  Draft: NETS Requirements/Implications
- NRC Study Date:870325 (Container 164, Folder 11)
  Summary of Committee's Fifth Meeting - March 4-5, 1987
- NRC Study Date:870416 (Container 164, Folder 12)
  Tentative Agenda, April 16-17, 1987, plus background materials
- NRC Study Date:870416 (Container 164, Folder 13)
  Final Agenda, April 16-17, plus "Statement of Task"
- NRC Study Date:870521 (Container 164, Folder 14)
  Draft: "Nationwide Emergency Telecommunications Service for National Security Telecommunications"
- NRC Study Date:870605 (Container 164, Folder 15)
  Committee Report Review: Second and Last Draft
- NRC Study Date:870321 (Container 164, Folder 16)
  Letter to Green from Johnson (regarding PB's call on his work)
- NRC Study Date:870202 (Container 164, Folder 17)
  Letter from Kriens (StrataCom.
- NRC Study Date:870324 (Container 164, Folder 18)
  Subcommittee on NETS Implementation vs. Requirements
- NRC Study Date:870801 (Container 164, Folder 19)
  Nationwide Emergency Telecommunications Service for National Security Telecommunications
- NRC Study Date:870901 (Container 164, Folder 20)
  Timing Reprints ("Synchronized Clock for DMS-100 Family", etc)
- C. Babbage Date:981107 (Container 165, Folder 1)
  CBI Initiatives by Year by Role
- C. Babbage Date:991001 (Container 165, Folder 2)
  Newsletter, Fall 1999
- C. Babbage Date:000329 (Container 165, Folder 3)
  Preliminary Ideas (response to Proposed Foundation to support the History of Computing)
- C. Babbage Date:000605 (Container 165, Folder 4)
  Invitation to "Unbundling History: the Emergence of the Software Product - 9/22/00
- C. Babbage Date:001013 (Container 165, Folder 5)
  Summary of Annual Meeting Activities
- C. Babbage Date:001101 (Container 165, Folder 6)
  Philanthropy, "The New Packard" (Packard's growing philanthropic empire)
- C. Babbage Date:001115 (Container 165, Folder 7)
  Advanced copy of "The Future of CBF - It's Ours to Choose"
- C. Babbage Date:001122 (Container 165, Folder 8)
  Grant recommendation form from Charitable Gift Fund for $25,000
- C. Babbage Date:001128 (Container 165, Folder 9)
  Information on the Feasibility Study
- C. Babbage Date:001208 (Container 165, Folder 10)
  Campaign Committee Minutes, Dec. 8, 2000
- C. Babbage Date:001219 (Container 165, Folder 11)
  Legal Review Committtee - documents in preparation with attorney
- C. Babbage Date:010202 (Container 165, Folder 12)
  Campaign Committee Minutes, Feb. 2, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010228 (Container 165, Folder 13)
  Sample Bylaws (for Claifornia Nonprofit Public Benefit Corp)
- C. Babbage Date:010306 (Container 165, Folder 14)
  Needed changes in the CBF infrastructure (from Coleman)
- C. Babbage Date:010309 (Container 165, Folder 15)
  Process for Changing the Bylaws for CBF
- C. Babbage Date:010322 (Container 165, Folder 16)
  List of those interviewed
- C. Babbage Date:010322 (Container 165, Folder 18)
  Feasibility Study Results
- C. Babbage Date:010327 (Container 165, Folder 19)
  Special Meeting of CBF on Bylaws
- C. Babbage Date:010328 (Container 165, Folder 20)
  Notice of CBF Meetings on April 13 and May 14, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010413 (Container 165, Folder 21)
  Agenda for Directors meeting on April 13
- C. Babbage Date:010425 (Container 165, Folder 22)
  Agenda for April 25 meeting, plus case statement
- C. Babbage Date:010513 (Container 165, Folder 23)
  Memos from Glaser with additional material for May 14
- C. Babbage Date:010514 (Container 165, Folder 24)
  Agenda for May 14, 2001, plus amended and restated bylaws
- C. Babbage Date:010514 (Container 165, Folder 25)
  Minutes from May 14, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010514 (Container 165, Folder 26)
  Report from Cortada on meeting from May 14, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010514 (Container 165, Folder 27)
  Progress report from the Legal Review Committee
- C. Babbage Date:010518 (Container 165, Folder 28)
  Trustees addresses and telephone information
- C. Babbage Date:010527 (Container 165, Folder 29)
  Draft: CBF History Portal and Design Overview & Request for Proposals
- C. Babbage Date:010530 (Container 165, Folder 30)
  Kaplan memo to PB - CBF records
- C. Babbage Date:010601 (Container 165, Folder 31)
  Material for teleconference on June 4, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010628 (Container 165, Folder 32)
  Agenda for June 28 teleconference 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010628 (Container 165, Folder 33)
  Minutes from June 28, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:010711 (Container 165, Folder 34)
  PB's large folder - materials from July 11 to October 4
- C. Babbage Date:010724 (Container 165, Folder 35)
  Information for meeting on July 27
- C. Babbage Date:010815 (Container 165, Folder 36)
  Minutes of May 14 - will be on August agenda
- C. Babbage Date:010830 (Container 165, Folder 37)
  Challenges of Preserving Computing History: Innovation, Mothballs, pioners, and Our Future Culture
- C. Babbage Date:010901 (Container 165, Folder 38)
  PB's comments on approach to the Internet Computer History Portal
- C. Babbage Date:010902 (Container 165, Folder 39)
  The Nature of Trustee Contributions
- C. Babbage Date:010905 (Container 165, Folder 40)
  Annual Trustee Meeting, Nov. 9 and 10, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:011108 (Container 165, Folder 41)
  Agenda for Campaign Committee, Nov. 8, 2001, teleconference
- C. Babbage Date:011116 (Container 165, Folder 42)
  Memo confirming lunch, Nov. 19, 2001
- C. Babbage Date:011109 (Container 165, Folder 43)
  Agenda for Board of Directors, Nov. 9, 2001 (and background info)
- C. Babbage Date:011119 (Container 165, Folder 44)
  PB's questions after Board meeting
- C. Babbage Date:011126 (Container 165, Folder 45)
  PB's memo to Galler (regarding his being the sec), plus minutes from 4/13 and 8/17)
- C. Babbage Date:011207 (Container 165, Folder 46)
  Agenda for Campaign committee, Dec. 7, 2001, teleconference
- C. Babbage Date:011214 (Container 165, Folder 47)
  Agenda for Board of Directors, Dec. 14, 2001 (and minutes from Nov. 9)
- Pro Bono Com Date:860210 (Container 166, Folder 1)
  Several articles, including "Packet-Switching Could Bring Back Single Network Concept"
- Pro Bono Com Date:860502 (Container 166, Folder 2)
  Wohlstetter's paper, "Beyond Simple Attack and Uncontrollable Retaliation"
- Pro Bono Com Date:860701 (Container 166, Folder 3)
  Wohlstetter's changes to "Beyond Simple Attack and Uncontrollable Retaliation"
- Pro Bono Com Date:860721 (Container 166, Folder 4)
  Articles on StrataCom taping the telephone market, and Equatorial cracking financial markets, etc.
- Pro Bono Com Date:860724 (Container 166, Folder 5)
  PB's discussion draft, "Thoughts on the Application of High-Speed Distributed Packet Switching
- Pro Bono Com Date:860727 (Container 166, Folder 6)
  Washington Post, "Building a Force for World War IV"
- Pro Bono Com Date:860820 (Container 166, Folder 7)
  Brody's redraft of PB's "The Application of Packet Switching to a More Survivable C3 Network (U)"
- Pro Bono Com Date:860826 (Container 166, Folder 8)
  Letter from Zraket to Wohlstetter responding to his letter on packet communications
- Pro Bono Com Date:860904 (Container 166, Folder 9)
  PB's consultant fee to Pan Heuristics Division, R&D Associates
- Pro Bono Com Date:860929 (Container 166, Folder 10)
  Wohlstetter's letter to PB and final report, "Electromagnetic Pulse (EMP)"
- Pro Bono Com Date:861009 (Container 166, Folder 11)
  PB's letter to Wohlstetter regarding the letter from Stratacom concerning their IPX switch
- Pro Bono Com Date:861105 (Container 166, Folder 12)
  RDA Logicon Travel re: hotel negotiations for Huntsville and Tampa